

Mustafa YASAR Amsterdam The Netherlands myasar0938@gmail.com +31 6 84593322 LinkedIn | GitHub Website

Full Stack Developer in continuous learning. After working in the Turkish National Police Academy and later as a lawyer, I am finally following my dream and dedicating myself to IT. My biggest goal is to combine the discipline with effective using of time, teamwork and the problem-solving experiences I gained from my past professions. My passions are to work with care, constantly improve myself, ask, learn and help others.

HTML	CSS	Bootstrap	Javascript	GIT
Rest API	Express.js	Node.js	MySQL	React.js

EXPERIENCE

Oct 2021 – july. 2022 HalalTravels, FullStack Web Developer (Full-time)

Developed and Supported Project using ReactJs, Javascript, NodeJs,

ExpressJs, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, MaterialUI, MySQL

-Designed the paged using Figma

-Created Dashboards

-Joined daily standup meetings

Aug 2021 –Oct. 2021 HalalTravels, FullStack Web Developer (Intern)

Developed FullStack Project using ReactJs, Javascript, NodeJs, HTML,

CSS, Bootstrap, MySQL

July 2019 – Apr 2021 Lawyer at Celik Law Consultant

EDUCATION

Aug 2022-Mar 2023 HackYourFuture, Web Development | Curriculum

7-months coding bootcamp with modules on HTML, CSS, JavaScript,

Node.js, Express.js, MySQL and React.js.

2020–2021 Anadolu University-Web Design and Development

2015 – 2019 Law Faculty at Gazi University

2012 – 2015 Turkish National Police Academy